Alejandra Lopez

13020 SW 92ndAVE
Miami, FL 33176
Phone:305-469-2429
alejandra_lopez_1@hotmail.com

QUALIFICATION SUMMARY

Experienced: Customer service professional with 5+ years of hospitality services

Efficient: Adept at consistently resolving client issues in a short time span. Learning fast.

Skilled: Possess exceptional customer service skills, with customers regularly recommending

on received support

Bilingual: Spanish-Native; English-fluent; Portuguese-Conversational.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2015-present

Mike's Marine Service

Yacht Stewardess/Detailing

Miami, FL

Service to the guests on board, making sure everything is in order and clean. Serve drinks and food to guests if necessary. Taking care of the details of the boat and providing full fine service to owners/guests on board.

2011-2014 Victoria Secret

Sales Representative Miami, FL

Sales associate, costumer care, and cashier.

2010 - 2010 Che Titos Argentinian Restaurant

Waitress Miami, FL

Taking orders, costumer care and satisfaction, being efficient and multi-task, and handling money

2006 - 2008 Mayumi Japanese Restaurant

Waitress helper Miami, FL

serving drinks, picking up dishes, and costumer care and satisfaction.

EDUCATION

2015- Miami International University of Art and Design Bachelors in Photography

Miami, FL

2012-2014 Miami Dade College Bachelors 2003-2006 High School Diploma (Felix Varela Senior High school)

Technical

Technical: Receive source data such as customer names, addresses. Credit card information. Perform data entry and retrieval with software such as Microsoft Office.

Able to set up a laptop, headphones, microphones, skype.